[Music]
a major challenge facing mining
companies
is the provision for rehabilitation
costs for end of mind closure
ensuring meets this challenge without
tying up cash
and other credit facilities with a
footprint spanning three continents
europe africa and australia through
intuitive member companies
lombard insurance asset insurer and
nordic guarantee
we can issue conditional on-demand
mining rehabilitation guarantees
that are irrevocable open-ended and a
good alternative to bank guarantees
ensuring and its member companies have
experienced
teams who are experts in mining
rehabilitation guarantees
contact us at insureity.globe